<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on SFDevs</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on SFDevs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:51:23 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sfdevs.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Senior Software Engineer</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/senior-software-engineer-prismatic-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 20:18:36 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/senior-software-engineer-prismatic-1/</guid><description>Hey.
Are you a super talented software engineer who is getting tired of working on the same boring stuff all the time? Maybe you’ve spent a bunch of time keeping up on the latest tech but don’t see many opportunities to use it in your day job? Perhaps you’re looking for the opportunity to play a key role in shaping the direction and culture of an exciting new startup, working alongside other talented and driven individuals such as yourself?</description></item><item><title>Software Architect</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-architect-prismatic-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 21:02:04 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-architect-prismatic-1/</guid><description>Hey.
Are you a super talented software architect who is getting tired of working on the same boring stuff all the time? Maybe you’ve spent a bunch of time keeping up on the latest tech but don’t see many opportunities to use it in your day job? Perhaps you’re looking for the opportunity to play a key role in shaping the direction and culture of an exciting new startup, working alongside other talented and driven individuals such as yourself?</description></item><item><title>An Apology to php[world] Attendees</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-10-17-phly-boy-phly-matthew-weier-o-phinney-an-apology-to-php-world-attendees/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-10-17-phly-boy-phly-matthew-weier-o-phinney-an-apology-to-php-world-attendees/</guid><description>Due to disorganization on my part, I accidentally booked php[world] 2019 to coincide with a family commitment.
After reviewing a variety of options, I let the organizers know last week that I could no longer attend. It&amp;rsquo;s a situation I hate, because there&amp;rsquo;s nobody to blame but me, and no matter what option I could come up with, somebody would end up disappointed or inconvenienced. For my part, my family had to come first.</description></item><item><title>Architecting UI Automation Projects for Maintainability</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-10-11-aligned-dev-architecting-ui-automation-projects-for-maintainability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-10-11-aligned-dev-architecting-ui-automation-projects-for-maintainability/</guid><description>#Architecting UI Automation Projects for Maintainability I published this article on November 10, 2015 on GeeksWithBlogs.net and have ported it here. I’ve been on a team now for a year+ and we’ve been using Selenium to automate acceptance tests before we consider a feature as completed. We’ve caught many regression issues that our Jasmine unit tests haven’t (which sometimes is a gap in our Jasmine tests, and sometimes is just a Knockout binding issue) and have avoided QA picking up buggy software for manually testing.</description></item><item><title>Chef Server and the risks of depending on the open source community</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-10-10-brian-olson-chef-server-and-the-risks-of-depending-on-the-open-source-community/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-10-10-brian-olson-chef-server-and-the-risks-of-depending-on-the-open-source-community/</guid><description>Continue reading Chef Server and the risks of depending on the open source&amp;#160;community</description></item><item><title>Looking For A New Adventure</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-10-03-phly-boy-phly-matthew-weier-o-phinney-looking-for-a-new-adventure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 20:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-10-03-phly-boy-phly-matthew-weier-o-phinney-looking-for-a-new-adventure/</guid><description>Update As of 2019-10-01, I am once again employed full-time. Thank you everyone who reached out!
Fourteen years ago, almost to the day, I received a job offer from Zend to join their nascent eBiz team, where I started contributing almost immediately to the yet-to-be-announced Zend Framework. Two years later, I joined the Zend Framework team full-time. A year later, I was promoted to Architect. A year after that, I was promoted to Project Lead of Zend Framework, a role I kept for the next ten years.</description></item><item><title>The Principles of Sowing and Reaping - Small Actions Over Time Add Up to Big Results</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-09-22-aligned-dev-the-principles-of-sowing-and-reaping-small-actions-over-time-add-up-to-big-results/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-09-22-aligned-dev-the-principles-of-sowing-and-reaping-small-actions-over-time-add-up-to-big-results/</guid><description>The Principles of Sowing and Reaping - Small Actions Over Time Add Up to Big Results The Bible tells us that we will reap what we sow. I believe that this happens mostly small incremental, day to day, moment to moment parts of life. It&amp;rsquo;s amazing how many examples this wisdom can be applied to in life and in software development. &amp;ldquo;Do not be deceived: God is not mocked, for whatever one sows, that will he also reap.</description></item><item><title>Paranoid Defensive Programming</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-09-11-brian-olson-paranoid-defensive-programming/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 08:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-09-11-brian-olson-paranoid-defensive-programming/</guid><description>Continue reading Paranoid Defensive Programming</description></item><item><title>Deploying WASM to Fastly&#39;s Edge</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-09-06-bryanburgers-deploying-wasm-to-fastly-s-edge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-09-06-bryanburgers-deploying-wasm-to-fastly-s-edge/</guid><description>Take Fastly&amp;rsquo;s Terrarium to a new level by deploying from a local build.</description></item><item><title>Book Stack 2019</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-09-06-aligned-dev-book-stack-2019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-09-06-aligned-dev-book-stack-2019/</guid><description>Books! I like to read. After a long day of computers at work, I find that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for me to get back onto a computer to learn after the kids are in bed. Here&amp;rsquo;s a stack of books I&amp;rsquo;ve read, am reading or hope to get to soon. Thank you to Omnitech for buying me many books over the years! From top to bottom: The Kindle PaperWhite I have way too many free books that I haven&amp;rsquo;t gotten to.</description></item><item><title>Loving Docker as a Windows guy: August 2019</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-08-10-brian-olson-loving-docker-as-a-windows-guy-august-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-08-10-brian-olson-loving-docker-as-a-windows-guy-august-2019/</guid><description>Continue reading Loving Docker as a Windows guy: August&amp;#160;2019</description></item><item><title>Hack Sioux Falls Final Projects (Spring 2019)</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-07-28-william-bushee-hack-sioux-falls-final-projects-spring-2019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 13:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-07-28-william-bushee-hack-sioux-falls-final-projects-spring-2019/</guid><description>Eighteen kids, eight meet-ups, zero shorted boards, seven blown LEDs, one burnt finger, and two months of fun &amp;amp; creativity. That sums up our third Hack Sioux Falls project hosted by Code Bootcamp School. When I first launched this project last year, I had no idea what to expect or what the kids would findRead more</description></item><item><title>PCI Access Without a Driver</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-07-09-bryanburgers-pci-access-without-a-driver/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-07-09-bryanburgers-pci-access-without-a-driver/</guid><description>Poke around in PCI memory space without writing a driver.</description></item><item><title>Managing Multiple PHP versions via the ondrej/php PPA</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-05-01-phly-boy-phly-matthew-weier-o-phinney-managing-multiple-php-versions-via-the-ondrej-php-ppa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-05-01-phly-boy-phly-matthew-weier-o-phinney-managing-multiple-php-versions-via-the-ondrej-php-ppa/</guid><description>Last week, I did some system updates, and then decided to compile the most recent PHP releases. I&amp;rsquo;ve used phpbrew to manage multiple PHP releases for a number of years, and having it install a new version is fairly routine.
Except this time, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Due to updates I installed, I was getting errors first with compiling the GD extension, then with ext-intl:
If you want Freetype support in ext-gd, you are expected to install the package libfreetype-dev.</description></item><item><title>How to Pass Variables to a Partial Template in Hugo</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-04-14-harmstyler-how-to-pass-variables-to-a-partial-template-in-hugo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 02:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-04-14-harmstyler-how-to-pass-variables-to-a-partial-template-in-hugo/</guid><description>As a developer, I want to keep my code as DRY as is feasible for the given project. In a Hugo project, that&amp;rsquo;s where the Partial templates come in. Partials are smaller, context-aware components in your list and page templates that can be used economically to keep your templating DRY. Partials, however, have one serious limitation, they&amp;rsquo;re cached during the build of a given page (or scope). Once a partial has been created, no outside logic can adjust what the partial returns (for the page).</description></item><item><title>Community blogs</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/list/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Hosting Hugo on Aws Cloudfront and Route53 Using Ansible</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-04-12-shellrunner-hosting-hugo-on-aws-cloudfront-and-route53-using-ansible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-04-12-shellrunner-hosting-hugo-on-aws-cloudfront-and-route53-using-ansible/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s really easy to to set up a website on AWS&amp;rsquo;s s3 service, but if you want to use a certificate (you do), it&amp;rsquo;s just a bit more work. With Ansible as my hammer, everything is a nail. Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick playbook I used to set up my site jxn.is to use cloudfront. This playbook creates the bucket, sets up an s3 website in the bucket, creates a cloudfront distribution with reasonable parameters, enables an existing Certificate Manager certificate on the site, and points DNS records at the cloudfront distribution.</description></item><item><title>Software Engineer</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-omnitech-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 16:20:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-omnitech-1/</guid><description>Omnitech is looking to add dedicated, eager, open-minded engineers to our Sioux Falls and Rapid City locations. Omnitech works with companies of all sizes, capabilities, and industries which including banking, medical and manufacturing. The one constant: investment in technology is critical to their business growth.</description></item><item><title>Getting Ec2 Instance Availability Zone With Curl or Powershell</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-03-10-shellrunner-getting-ec2-instance-availability-zone-with-curl-or-powershell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 15:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-03-10-shellrunner-getting-ec2-instance-availability-zone-with-curl-or-powershell/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of AWS&amp;rsquo;s SDK&amp;rsquo;s and API tools because they&amp;rsquo;re so comprehensive and easy to use, in general, but I sometimes forget that there&amp;rsquo;s another good, even simpler API for getting data from some AWS resources&amp;hellip; the magical http://169.254.169.254/ http endpoint! This endpoint provides read-only metadata about resources once you have access, and doesn&amp;rsquo;t require additional authentication. This is very handy, for instance, when a client gives me SSH or RDP access to an EC2 instance and I need to know its size, network info, or in this case what Availability Zone it is in:</description></item><item><title>DSU / AT&amp;T Hackathon</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-02-27-william-bushee-dsu-at-t-hackathon/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-02-27-william-bushee-dsu-at-t-hackathon/</guid><description>We did it. We challenged 15 DSU students to solve real-world problems for first responders. And then we gave them 48-hours to research, prototype a solution, and then pitch those solutions to a panel of first responders “There are companies spending millions of dollars on solutions that are not this good.” A response from oneRead more</description></item><item><title>Contrast Ratio Calculator</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-02-17-harmstyler-contrast-ratio-calculator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 17:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-02-17-harmstyler-contrast-ratio-calculator/</guid><description>Making sure webistes are accessible is a big deal these days. Websites should be mindful of their audience to make sure people with disabilities are not excluded from the site content. Color contrasts between foregrounds and backgrounds is an easy miss when checking that a site is accessible, but one that is vital to hard of sight users.</description></item><item><title>Trying Out Hugo</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-02-08-shellrunner-trying-out-hugo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-02-08-shellrunner-trying-out-hugo/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty heavily reorganizing and simplifying my life lately, so it was time to replace the tired old Wordpress blog at ShellRunner with something more deserving. Wordpress has been a great platform over the years, but as a constant target of attacks, it could also be a pain to keep up. Also, it&amp;rsquo;s much more fun to write my posts in Markdown, instead of in a browser editor. This is post #1 trying out Hugo, a fast static generator written in Go with a lot of features.</description></item><item><title>Real-Quick…Hack Sioux Falls Tickets on Sale Now (LIMITED)</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-01-27-william-bushee-real-quick-hack-sioux-falls-tickets-on-sale-now-limited/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-01-27-william-bushee-real-quick-hack-sioux-falls-tickets-on-sale-now-limited/</guid><description>Teaching Kids About Electronics Hack Sioux Falls takes kids on a journey that teaches them about electronics, hardware, software, soldering, functional design, user design, and creative thinking. The official challenge will be announced in about a week, but it will be a lot of fun to build and has plenty of room for kids toRead more</description></item><item><title>Showing Firefox close tab on tab hover</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-01-03-austin-hanson-showing-firefox-close-tab-on-tab-hover/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 14:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2019-01-03-austin-hanson-showing-firefox-close-tab-on-tab-hover/</guid><description>I switched from Chrome to Firefox a few months ago. For the most part…it feels roughly the same but there was one subtle difference that finally irked me to the point of googling: having to right click on a tab to close it. In Chrome, when you hover over the active tab the close button pops up. This means you can pretty easily close multiple tabs by clicking the last tab on the right, clicking close, and then repeatedly clicking as the close tab appears in each successive tab.</description></item><item><title>Avoiding Route Collision in eZ Platform</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2018-12-19-harmstyler-avoiding-route-collision-in-ez-platform/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2018-12-19-harmstyler-avoiding-route-collision-in-ez-platform/</guid><description>eZ Platform boils down to a set of Symfony bundles that give you a nice way of managing content for your users. With these bundles, eZ reserves some routing paths for internal or admin use, paths that you might want for your own app. If you ever run across a path you want to use for your app, and not break an internal eZ feature, there is a simple solution: change the path config.</description></item><item><title>About SFDevs</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:17:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/about/</guid><description>Nestled in the middle of the Heartland you&amp;rsquo;ll find Sioux Falls, SD. Sioux Falls has a booming developer community, we&amp;rsquo;re also known as the &amp;ldquo;Silicon Prairie.&amp;rdquo;
The Sioux Falls Developer&amp;rsquo;s Group is open to developers in the area. Each month we bring in speakers to present on a wide variety of software development topics. Once a year, we put on a developer centric conference, South Dakota Code Camp.
Site Design: TEMPLATED.</description></item><item><title>Submit a job</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/submit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:17:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/submit/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Template Literals and Tagged Templates</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2018-09-02-of-miles-rausch-template-literals-and-tagged-templates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 02:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2018-09-02-of-miles-rausch-template-literals-and-tagged-templates/</guid><description>Continue reading &amp;ldquo;Template Literals and Tagged Templates&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Extending the Iterator Trait in Rust</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2018-01-11-bryanburgers-extending-the-iterator-trait-in-rust/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2018-01-11-bryanburgers-extending-the-iterator-trait-in-rust/</guid><description>Extending the Iterator trait in Rust by adding a new function for a new type of iterator transformation.</description></item><item><title>C# .NET Core, Console App, DI, and Serilog - Getting Started</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-12-21-austin-hanson-c-net-core-console-app-di-and-serilog-getting-started/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 15:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-12-21-austin-hanson-c-net-core-console-app-di-and-serilog-getting-started/</guid><description>My day job involves a lot of .NET Core development and a whole lot of logging. As a result, I’ve become accustomed to having logs when I need them. When working on pet projects I usually don’t spend as much time on the “niceties” of life. Lately I’ve started doing it a little more and wanted to detail some findings.
Command line apps with CommandLineApplication # There’s a lot of resources out there on using Microsoft’s new CommandLineApplication.</description></item><item><title>Inspecting OpenEdge metadata with SQL</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-12-03-zedfox-inspecting-openedge-metadata-with-sql/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 05:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-12-03-zedfox-inspecting-openedge-metadata-with-sql/</guid><description>Inspecting OpenEdge metadata with SQL OpenEdge&amp;#8217;s virtual system tables (VSTs) provide excellent statistics that help in database development and maintenance. This article shows a few SQL statements that help reveal information about the database. SQL to query metadata Show all VST tables that contain metadata. [crayon-5dab1e8d8058e502861965/] Find columns in a table [crayon-5dab1e8d80594075176520/] Show all the [&amp;#8230;]</description></item><item><title>Viewing query plan with SQL in OpenEdge</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-12-03-zedfox-viewing-query-plan-with-sql-in-openedge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 02:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-12-03-zedfox-viewing-query-plan-with-sql-in-openedge/</guid><description>Viewing query plan with SQL in OpenEdge It is important to review query plan produced by the database and improve queries from time to time. OpenEdge generates query plan for the queries you write. This article shows how to view query plan in OpenEdge. View query plan Let&amp;#8217;s say the query below is taking a [&amp;#8230;]</description></item><item><title>Create table with SQL in OpenEdge</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-12-03-zedfox-create-table-with-sql-in-openedge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2017 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-12-03-zedfox-create-table-with-sql-in-openedge/</guid><description>Create table with SQL in OpenEdge One of the most basic and important database objects is tables. We can create tables with either ABL or SQL. This article discusses how to create table with SQL and the various datatypes and constraints that can be used to create them. Documentation of create table is covered quite [&amp;#8230;]</description></item><item><title>Slides and Demo for Building Progressive Web Apps using CFML</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-07-20-of-miles-rausch-slides-and-demo-for-building-progressive-web-apps-using-cfml/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-07-20-of-miles-rausch-slides-and-demo-for-building-progressive-web-apps-using-cfml/</guid><description>Thanks everyone for coming to my talk at cf.Objective() 2017! If you missed my talk, or just want to learn more about Progressive Web Apps, feel free to browse the links below. Browse the slides at http://slides.com/awayken/2017cfobjective Find the code at https://github.com/awayken/pwa-marketing-site</description></item><item><title>Using() block hell in C#</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-04-28-austin-hanson-using-block-hell-in-c/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2017 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-04-28-austin-hanson-using-block-hell-in-c/</guid><description>So the other day I was working on transforming streams for an encryption layer for work. I ended up having some code that looked similar to this:
public async Task SendAsync(byte[] data, Delegate next) { using (var stream = ...) { using (var encryptStream = ...) { using (var encodeStream = ...) { using (var reader = ...) { await next(...); } } } } } public async Task RecieveAsync(byte[] data, Delegate next) { using (var stream = .</description></item><item><title>Add React Hot Reloading to create-react-app</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-04-06-josh-broton-add-react-hot-reloading-to-create-react-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2017-04-06-josh-broton-add-react-hot-reloading-to-create-react-app/</guid><description>I love create-react-app. I&amp;#8217;ve used it as the boilerplate generator for the last 4 projects I&amp;#8217;ve worked on. I&amp;#8217;ve tried other React boilerplates, but always come back because of it&amp;#8217;s great foundation, as well as it&amp;#8217;s ability to be ejected &amp;#8230; Continued
The post Add React Hot Reloading to create-react-app appeared first on joshbroton.com.</description></item><item><title>powershell bashrc equivalent</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-08-09-sclarson-powershell-bashrc-equivalent/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-08-09-sclarson-powershell-bashrc-equivalent/</guid><description>One complaint I hear a lot from the linux users who have to do windows admin work for a random project the most common thing I hear a complaint about is a bashrc equivalent. I&amp;#8217;ve been asked about it a few times and knew you could do this at the local user level and replied &amp;#8230; Continue reading powershell bashrc equivalent</description></item><item><title>PostCSS: A Dumb Name For an Awesome Thing</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-06-22-of-miles-rausch-postcss-a-dumb-name-for-an-awesome-thing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-06-22-of-miles-rausch-postcss-a-dumb-name-for-an-awesome-thing/</guid><description>Continue reading &amp;ldquo;PostCSS: A Dumb Name For an Awesome Thing&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>Windows XP and Slow HTTP Requests</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-06-21-opello-windows-xp-and-slow-http-requests/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-06-21-opello-windows-xp-and-slow-http-requests/</guid><description>This week at work I was faced with a bug that manifested as Windows XP clients being slower to access parts of a web interface than Windows 7 or 10. This was strange because in Wireshark the requests looked basically the same.
It turned out that the embedded system hosting the web interface was rejecting Ethernet frames larger than 1500 bytes. This was most likely because of a misinterpretation of the MTU as referring to the frame size (at layer 2) instead of the payload size (at layer 3).</description></item><item><title>So You Want to Change the Gravity Forms Form Tag…</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-04-01-josh-broton-so-you-want-to-change-the-gravity-forms-form-tag/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-04-01-josh-broton-so-you-want-to-change-the-gravity-forms-form-tag/</guid><description>I had an interesting request from a client today. They use Pardot to integrate with the forms on their old website, and wanted to do the same with their new WordPress theme. We&amp;#8217;re using the always spectacular Gravity Forms for &amp;#8230; Continued
The post So You Want to Change the Gravity Forms Form Tag&amp;#8230; appeared first on joshbroton.com.</description></item><item><title>NameSilo API from PowerShell</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-02-14-opello-namesilo-api-from-powershell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-02-14-opello-namesilo-api-from-powershell/</guid><description>A friend asked several people on irc about NameSilo&amp;rsquo;s API and dynamic DNS entries. He found a PowerShell script to update a subdomain with the current IP address of the system running the script. The subdomain detail was the crux of the question: how to get it to update a &amp;ldquo;naked&amp;rdquo; domain. Several of us read through the API reference but the dnsUpdateRecord function didn&amp;rsquo;t explain how to update the base domain&amp;rsquo;s A record.</description></item><item><title>Linux Performance</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-02-08-sclarson-linux-performance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-02-08-sclarson-linux-performance/</guid><description>I&amp;#8217;ve been asked a few times for how to find performance issues around various types on linux. The old man in me wants to tell people to read the man pages. The nice person in me says &amp;#8220;Read and watch Brendan Gregg&amp;#8217;s material. It is amazingly well done.&amp;#8221; He even has content specific to EC2 &amp;#8230; Continue reading Linux Performance</description></item><item><title>Churn (code)</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-02-08-sclarson-churn-code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2016 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-02-08-sclarson-churn-code/</guid><description>One of the most useful things when you&amp;#8217;re new to a codebase can be to look at version control and find out who owns what parts of the codebase and how where are the hottest spots in the codebase. Corey Haines posted a gist years ago of a great way to get the second part &amp;#8230; Continue reading Churn (code)</description></item><item><title>Change is Scary; The Future is Bright</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-01-25-josh-broton-change-is-scary-the-future-is-bright/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2016-01-25-josh-broton-change-is-scary-the-future-is-bright/</guid><description>After two awesome years, it&amp;#8217;s time. My last day at Lemonly will be this Friday, January 29th. That&amp;#8217;s a hard thing for me to write. I&amp;#8217;ve been at Lemonly since December 2013, two of the best years of my life. &amp;#8230; Continued
The post Change is Scary; The Future is Bright appeared first on joshbroton.com.</description></item><item><title>Python and JSON-RPC</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2013-12-01-opello-python-and-json-rpc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2013 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/posts/external_posts/2013-12-01-opello-python-and-json-rpc/</guid><description>In playing with Bitcoin, in this case specifically with the bitcoin-qt client, I found myself wanting to more granularly control which of my coins I spent. This probably isn&amp;rsquo;t something most people care about, or maybe even solve by using multiple wallets, but I thought that it would be nice to choose which addresses were used for transactions. I found that I was not alone in that desire. But sadly, the patch has yet to be merged despite going through a number of iterations.</description></item></channel></rss>