<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on SFDevs</title>
    <link>https://sfdevs.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on SFDevs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:51:23 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sfdevs.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Engineer - Windows</title>
      <link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/devops-engineer-windows-tguymm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 19:26:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/devops-engineer-windows-tguymm/</guid>
      <description>Summary CentralSquare is the largest public safety software company in the world. We run solutions that provide essential public safety services to over half of North America. We want you to build and maintain solutionsthat make a real difference in the lives of citizens throughout the Americas improving, health, safety, and justice. This isn’t your typical sell-ads and mine-personal-data software job. Join us and make a positive difference in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-omnitech-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 16:20:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-omnitech-1/</guid>
      <description>Are you a team-oriented engineer? Enthusiastic about technology? Omnitech is looking to add dedicated, eager, open-minded engineers to our Sioux Falls and Rapid City locations.
Omnitech is a South Dakota engineering firm headquartered out of Sioux Falls South, Dakota. Established in 1998 with a passion for investing in people while creating technology solutions with a foundation of honesty and integrity. At our core, we are a team of curious software and data engineers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sr. C#/.NET Engineer</title>
      <link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/sr-c-net-engineer-bkfqnm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 14:57:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/sr-c-net-engineer-bkfqnm/</guid>
      <description>Summary  The Senior Software Engineer is responsible for enhancing and maintaining existing applications, troubleshooting, and resolving defects in an agile team environment. The Senior Software Engineer conducts complex work with limited supervision and a wide latitude for independent judgment. The Software Engineer must demonstrate advanced technical proficiency in his/her personal work as well as contribute to the team’s continued success by increasing his/her technical knowledge. This is sometimes a customer facing role, and the Software Engineer will communicate professionally and positively with CentralSquare clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Engineer - Unix</title>
      <link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/devops-engineer-unix-pmjgvw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 17:21:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/devops-engineer-unix-pmjgvw/</guid>
      <description>CentralSquare is the largest public safety software company in the world. We run solutions that provide essential public safety services to over half of North America. We want you to build and maintain solutions that make a real difference in the lives of citizens throughout the Americas improving, health, safety, and justice. This isn’t your typical sell-ads and mine-personal-data software job. Join us and make a positive difference in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual studio 2019 launch</title>
      <link>https://sfdevs.com/events/visual-studio-2019-launch-259527992/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 08:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/visual-studio-2019-launch-259527992/</guid>
      <description>Join us to go over the new features in visual studio 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Software Engineer</title>
      <link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/senior-software-engineer-533482100/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 15:41:23 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/senior-software-engineer-533482100/</guid>
      <description>For 60 years, Raven has developed, marketed, and produced technical solutions to great challenges. Utilizing our strength in engineering, manufacturing, and technological innovation, Raven today is a leader in precision agriculture, high performance specialty films, and situational awareness markets. Our purpose to Solve Great Challenges is bold and authentic; it keeps us grounded in markets that have meaning, provide profitable growth, and align with our values.
Raven Applied Technology is dedicated to feeding a growing world population.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submit a job</title>
      <link>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/submit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:17:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/submit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>