<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Jobs on SFDevs</title>
  <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/"/>
  <updated>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:51:23 -0500</updated>
  <subtitle>Recent Job Listings on SFDevs</subtitle>
  <author>
    <name>SFDevs</name>
    <email>sfdevs@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="https://gohugo.io/" version="1.0">
    Hugo -- gohugo.io
  </generator>
  <icon>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/images/share_jobs_400.png</icon>
  <logo>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/images/share_jobs.png</logo>
  <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/</id>

    
      
        
  <entry>
    <title>Software Engineer - Full Stack</title>
    <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-full-stack-carsforsale-1/"/>
    <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-full-stack-carsforsale-1/</id>
    <updated>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 12:26:12 -0500</updated>
    <summary>Job Description Carsforsale.com is a rapidly growing company and marketing leader in the automotive category looking to expand our Software Development Team. The Carsforsale.com team is currently concentrated on scaling web products that reach millions of car buyers and launching cutting-edge web and mobile applications. We are currently looking for highly qualified, motivated Software Developers to join this team. As Carsforsale.com continues to grow and evolve into a diversified Technology company, we want to bring the best developers available onto our team!</summary>
  </entry>
        
      
    
      
        
  <entry>
    <title>DevOps Engineer - Windows</title>
    <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/devops-engineer-windows-tguymm/"/>
    <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/devops-engineer-windows-tguymm/</id>
    <updated>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 19:26:04 -0500</updated>
    <summary>At CentralSquare, the DevOps Engineer works closely with Product, Engineering, Operations and Support teams. Individuals in this role use their system and networking knowledge to help design reliable, scalable, and cost-effective systems that meet business needs. DevOps Engineers must ensure that on-premise and hosted systems remain healthy.</summary>
  </entry>
        
      
    
      
        
  <entry>
    <title>Software Engineer</title>
    <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-omnitech-1/"/>
    <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-omnitech-1/</id>
    <updated>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 16:20:05 -0500</updated>
    <summary>Are you a team-oriented engineer? Enthusiastic about technology? Omnitech is looking to add dedicated, eager, open-minded engineers to our Sioux Falls and Rapid City locations.
Omnitech is a South Dakota engineering firm headquartered out of Sioux Falls South, Dakota. Established in 1998 with a passion for investing in people while creating technology solutions with a foundation of honesty and integrity. At our core, we are a team of curious software and data engineers.</summary>
  </entry>
        
      
    
      
        
  <entry>
    <title>Sr. C#/.NET Engineer</title>
    <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/sr-c-net-engineer-bkfqnm/"/>
    <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/sr-c-net-engineer-bkfqnm/</id>
    <updated>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 14:57:39 -0500</updated>
    <summary>Summary  The Senior Software Engineer is responsible for enhancing and maintaining existing applications, troubleshooting, and resolving defects in an agile team environment. The Senior Software Engineer conducts complex work with limited supervision and a wide latitude for independent judgment. The Software Engineer must demonstrate advanced technical proficiency in his/her personal work as well as contribute to the team’s continued success by increasing his/her technical knowledge. This is sometimes a customer facing role, and the Software Engineer will communicate professionally and positively with CentralSquare clients.</summary>
  </entry>
        
      
    
      
        
  <entry>
    <title>DevOps Engineer - Unix</title>
    <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/devops-engineer-unix-pmjgvw/"/>
    <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/devops-engineer-unix-pmjgvw/</id>
    <updated>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 17:21:21 -0500</updated>
    <summary>CentralSquare is the largest public safety software company in the world. We run solutions that provide essential public safety services to over half of North America. We want you to build and maintain solutions that make a real difference in the lives of citizens throughout the Americas improving, health, safety, and justice. This isn’t your typical sell-ads and mine-personal-data software job. Join us and make a positive difference in the world.</summary>
  </entry>
        
      
    
      
        
      
    
</feed>
