<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Jobs on SFDevs</title>
  <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/"/>
  <updated>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:51:23 -0500</updated>
  <subtitle>Recent Job Listings on SFDevs</subtitle>
  <author>
    <name>SFDevs</name>
    <email>sfdevs@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="https://gohugo.io/" version="1.0">
    Hugo -- gohugo.io
  </generator>
  <icon>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/images/share_jobs_400.png</icon>
  <logo>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/images/share_jobs.png</logo>
  <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/</id>

    
      
        
  <entry>
    <title>Database Developer</title>
    <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/database-developer-carsforsale-2/"/>
    <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/database-developer-carsforsale-2/</id>
    <updated>Wed, 22 May 2019 09:39:35 -0500</updated>
    <summary>Job Description Carsforsale.com is a rapidly growing company and marketing leader in the automotive category looking to expand our Data Team. The Carsforsale.com team is currently concentrated on scaling web products that reach millions of car buyers and launching cutting-edge web and mobile applications.
This position will involve database design and development of solutions and implementing a deliberate architecture for data integration and data movement across the organization.
 This is a full-time position located in our Sioux Falls, SD corporate headquarters.</summary>
  </entry>
        
      
    
      
        
  <entry>
    <title>Full-Stack Developer</title>
    <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/full-stack-developer-electric-pulp-1/"/>
    <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/full-stack-developer-electric-pulp-1/</id>
    <updated>Thu, 02 May 2019 15:34:43 -0500</updated>
    <summary>As a Full-Stack Developer at Electric Pulp, you’ll be integral to the success of the project, working with our project managers, designers and production team to implement a wide range of functionality. Projects involve working with frameworks like Laravel, Vue, React and platforms like WordPress, Shopify and Magento, to name a few.</summary>
  </entry>
        
      
    
      
        
      
    
      
        
      
    
      
        
  <entry>
    <title>Software Engineer</title>
    <link href="https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-omnitech-1/"/>
    <id>https://sfdevs.com/jobs/software-engineer-omnitech-1/</id>
    <updated>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 16:20:05 -0500</updated>
    <summary>Are you a team-oriented engineer? Enthusiastic about technology? Omnitech is looking to add dedicated, eager, open-minded engineers to our Sioux Falls and Rapid City locations.
Omnitech is a South Dakota engineering firm headquartered out of Sioux Falls South, Dakota. Established in 1998 with a passion for investing in people while creating technology solutions with a foundation of honesty and integrity. At our core, we are a team of curious software and data engineers.</summary>
  </entry>
        
      
    
      
        
      
    
      
        
      
    
      
        
      
    
</feed>
