<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Past Events on SFDevs</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/</link><description>Recent content in Past Events on SFDevs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 10:06:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sfdevs.com/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using the Compiler API in Real-World Scenarios</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/using-the-compiler-api-in-real-world-scenarios-269602758/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 10:06:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/using-the-compiler-api-in-real-world-scenarios-269602758/</guid><description>With the Compiler API, .NET developers have the ability to use the wealth of information it provides on their code for inspection and modification. Knowing how to use the Compiler API can, however, may seem like a daunting task. In this session, I&amp;rsquo;ll demonstrate a number of real-world examples that use the Compiler API to provide useful functionality and features via analyzers, refactorings, and .NET Core tools. You&amp;rsquo;ll see how straightforward this API is, and you&amp;rsquo;ll understand how to apply it in your own applications.</description></item><item><title>Fundamentals of networking for web developers</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/fundamentals-of-networking-for-web-developers-268122064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 15:02:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/fundamentals-of-networking-for-web-developers-268122064/</guid><description>We have all used the internet. Some of us might even have written code for a web site. Now let&amp;rsquo;s demystify how it all works. Things to be covered:
Basics of networking and networking tools How do domain names and addresses work Network structure and topology Protocols, layers, and packets Network factors affecting web reliability and performance The future of web networks Carsforsale.com will be providing pizza and beverages for this meetup.</description></item><item><title>What's new in C# 8? with Jason Bock</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/what-s-new-in-c-8-with-jason-bock-263404766/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 18:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/what-s-new-in-c-8-with-jason-bock-263404766/</guid><description>C# is an open-source, mature object oriented language, used by millions of .NET developers, yet its evolution is still underway. In this session, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover the latest features that have been added to C#8 and how they work in detail so you&amp;rsquo;ll know when to use them effectively in your new .NET projects. You&amp;rsquo;ll also see the direction C# may be going with future versions of C#.</description></item><item><title>Intro to GraphQL</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/intro-to-graphql-262809318/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 08:32:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/intro-to-graphql-262809318/</guid><description>Slides link Github Repo
GraphQL is growing rapidly in popularity as an alternative to REST. But, what is GraphQL and what differentiates it from REST? What benefits does it offer for both the user and developer?
Over the course of the talk we&amp;rsquo;ll be diving into the world of GraphQL covering advantages and difficulties of developing a GraphQL API. From a starting point of defining new vocabulary in use with GraphQL we&amp;rsquo;ll advance to more difficult topics such as pagination, authentication and schema stitching.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Unit Testing Workshop (2 of 2)</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/getting-started-with-unit-testing-workshop-2-of-2-261680554/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 13:51:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/getting-started-with-unit-testing-workshop-2-of-2-261680554/</guid><description>Join Omnitech Software Engineer Kevin Logan for part TWO of a lunch-hour dive into Unit Testing.
The combined talks will include a short introduction to unit testing in general, along with some hands-on-keyboard work following Kevin with C# MVC API unit tests. The lessons will be broadly applicable to unit testing in general, including other programming languages.
The second meeting will give us time to talk about experiences and look into integration testing in .</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Unit Testing Workshop (1 of 2)</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/getting-started-with-unit-testing-workshop-1-of-2-261422446/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 09:03:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/getting-started-with-unit-testing-workshop-1-of-2-261422446/</guid><description>Join Omnitech Software Engineer Kevin Logan for part one of a lunch-hour dive into Unit Testing.
The combined talks will include a short introduction to unit testing in general, along with some hands-on-keyboard work following Kevin with C# MVC API unit tests. The lessons will be broadly applicable to unit testing in general, including other programming languages.
To make the best of this workshop, please download repos and tools beforehand and do a little preparation:</description></item><item><title>Visual studio 2019 launch</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/visual-studio-2019-launch-259527992/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:32:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/visual-studio-2019-launch-259527992/</guid><description>Join us to go over the new features in visual studio 2019.</description></item><item><title>.NET Conf Live Day 3</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/net-conf-live-day-3-254620766/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 13:09:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/net-conf-live-day-3-254620766/</guid><description>https://www.dotnetconf.net/agenda
A group of people who deal with .Net regularly will be meeting in the room next to the usual meeting room at Raven Industries to watch some of the streamed sessions throughout the day.</description></item><item><title>.NET Conf Live Day 2</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/net-conf-live-day-2-254620738/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 13:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/net-conf-live-day-2-254620738/</guid><description>https://www.dotnetconf.net/agenda
A group of people who deal with .Net regularly will be meeting in the room next to the usual meeting room at Raven Industries to watch some of the streamed sessions throughout the day.</description></item><item><title>.NET Conf Live Day 1</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/net-conf-live-day-1-254182005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 13:49:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/net-conf-live-day-1-254182005/</guid><description>https://www.dotnetconf.net/agenda
A group of people who deal with .Net regularly will be meeting in the room next to the usual meeting room at Raven Industries to watch some of the streamed sessions throughout the day.</description></item><item><title>Mesos, Marathon, and Docker</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/mesos-marathon-and-docker-248071996/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/mesos-marathon-and-docker-248071996/</guid><description>What is Apache Mesos? What is Mesosphere’s Marathon? How do they work and work together? As a developer, how can I wire these up in order to execute applications in a compute environment?
Mesos is a cluster manager that abstracts computing resources away from machines enabling both fault tolerance and distributed elastic systems. Marathon enables orchestration for Docker containers, including persistence and high availability. The combination of these three software packages enables a proven framework for container orchestration and high compute resource utilization over large node clusters.</description></item><item><title>Learn About Blockchains</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/learn-about-blockchains-246909966/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 14:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/learn-about-blockchains-246909966/</guid><description>What is blockchain technology?How does it work and what applications exist?As a developer, how do I get started implementing my own blockchain?
Blockchain, the underlying technology in cryptocurrency is all the hype right now with some cryptocurrency values skyrocketing over 1500% last year! Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss how blockchain works and how it is useful in markets beyond cryptocurrency. Learn how to get started implementing your own blockchain!
&amp;ldquo;Email is to the internet as cryptocurrency is to the blockchain.</description></item><item><title>Hypervisors, VMs, and containers oh my!</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/hypervisors-vms-and-containers-oh-my-240785001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 08:46:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/hypervisors-vms-and-containers-oh-my-240785001/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s Docker? How does it differ from a VM? How does this differ from a process manager? In this talk we&amp;rsquo;ll cover: what Docker is, how it differs in given environments, and how you can benefit from containers today. I&amp;rsquo;ll briefly touch on docker-compose to prepare you for a talk on Docker orchestration.</description></item><item><title>Progressive Web Apps with Daniel Black</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/progressive-web-apps-with-daniel-black-239637490/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 10:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/progressive-web-apps-with-daniel-black-239637490/</guid><description>Progressive web apps (PWAs) close the gap and blur the lines between native apps and web apps. Daniel will introduce PWAs, including service workers, push notifications, app icons, offline capabilities, the app manifest, and browser support. He will also discuss practical applications and case studies to give business insight into this newer technology.
Daniel Black is an Android Software Engineer with Carsforsale.com - Thit Team</description></item><item><title>Knowing things work instead of thinking things work</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/knowing-things-work-instead-of-thinking-things-work-238594810/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 13:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/knowing-things-work-instead-of-thinking-things-work-238594810/</guid><description>Production can be a scary environment. Sometimes things are working great and sometimes they&amp;rsquo;re a complete dumpster fire. How do you know your current status? How do you know where your problem is or which server is causing the degradation? In this talk we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss a journey from no application performance monitoring(apm) to &amp;ldquo;good enough to troubleshoot today&amp;rdquo; apm and where we continued after our tire fire was turned back into a normal day.</description></item><item><title>From JavaScript Mess to Cleaner Code with Kevin Logan</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/from-javascript-mess-to-cleaner-code-with-kevin-logan-238242890/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 11:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/from-javascript-mess-to-cleaner-code-with-kevin-logan-238242890/</guid><description>As web development grows in popularity and the proliferation of JavaScript tools and frameworks continues, it is easier to produce large applications filled with unreadable or unmaintainable JavaScript. In this talk, Kevin Logan will draw on his years of experience working on a large JavaScript-heavy application. Kevin will describe how he has used methodologies, like SOLID and good naming practices, to improve code. The talk will demonstrate updating a jQuery-driven UI application using tools and priniciples like OOP, inversion of control, Typescript, unit testing, and DOM data-binding.</description></item><item><title>React Native for Mobile Apps with Gage Herrmann</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/react-native-for-mobile-apps-with-gage-herrmann-235767551/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 18:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/react-native-for-mobile-apps-with-gage-herrmann-235767551/</guid><description>Learn a new way to create native, cross-platform mobile apps using the web-development tools you already know. These are not hybrid apps, or web-view apps. These are real native apps that happen to be written in JavaScript (or any language that compiles to JavaScript).
Presenter: Gage Herrmann, mobile developer at Sterling e-Marketing</description></item><item><title>HapiJS Workshop</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/hapijs-workshop-234277850/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 17:03:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/hapijs-workshop-234277850/</guid><description>DocuTAP will be hosting a HapiJS workshop on Tues Oct 25th. Bring your own laptop, newcomers to nodejs or web development are welcome. We&amp;rsquo;ll have a few people with experience in nodejs available to help explain exercises and their solutions available.
https://github.com/hapijs/makemehapi</description></item><item><title>Talk Web Assembly with Jason Bock</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/talk-web-assembly-with-jason-bock-233590064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/talk-web-assembly-with-jason-bock-233590064/</guid><description>Assembling the Web - A Tour of WebAssembly
WebAssembly. It&amp;rsquo;s coming to JavaScript. But&amp;hellip;what exactly is it? Is it a new VM? A way to create a binary version of JavaScript? A new standard to get everyone to code in C/C++ for the web? In this session, we&amp;rsquo;ll demystify WebAssembly, demonstrate exactly what it is, and provide insight into how this will affect JavaScript and web development in the future.</description></item><item><title>Android Development</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/android-development-232424526/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 14:45:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/android-development-232424526/</guid><description>Taking a look at the current state of Android development, I hope to get you started building apps on the platform with powerful but sometimes unconventional techniques including:- UI components- Dependency Injection- Reactive Extensions- UI Libraries (ButterKnife / Databinding)</description></item><item><title>Writing Safer Code with Swift – Gage Herrmann</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/writing-safer-code-with-swift-gage-herrmann-231096032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 08:41:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/writing-safer-code-with-swift-gage-herrmann-231096032/</guid><description>A lot of the languages we use are extremely flexible and powerful. C# and Java allow you to write complex code that does a lot of things. They let you get stuff done, but they can also get you into a lot of trouble.
A few new languages have appeared in the last few years that are recognizing the importance of protecting programmers from themselves while remaining flexible and powerful.</description></item><item><title>Git Workshop</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/git-workshop-230630203/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 06:52:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/git-workshop-230630203/</guid><description>MWOP and Seth Larson are putting together a patchwork inspired git workshop(bring your own device). Whether you&amp;rsquo;re new to git or quite experienced hopefully you can come learn something. The workshop centers around content produced by github is designed to be hands-on and self paced, but we&amp;rsquo;ll have more than a few mentors available for questions.
If you&amp;rsquo;re already using git (or another dvcs) and want to talk workflow, or related things like continuous integration/delivery feel free to come tell others what you&amp;rsquo;re doing or ask what they&amp;rsquo;re doing.</description></item><item><title>Rapid Application Development using Cloud Services</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/rapid-application-development-using-cloud-services-227914597/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2016 10:03:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/rapid-application-development-using-cloud-services-227914597/</guid><description>Abel Wang and Valerie Vogt (from Microsoft) will be presenting on Rapid Application Development (RAD) using cloud services - see how you can quickly build functionality by connecting multiple applications, such as Office 365, Dynamics CRM, Facebook, and Twitter using Azure PaaS and C#. Then manage your application by leveraging DevOps in the modern world using TFS/VSTS.</description></item><item><title>Making Git work for you</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/making-git-work-for-you-227140442/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 13:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/making-git-work-for-you-227140442/</guid><description>Are you using Git but are worried you aren&amp;rsquo;t leveraging it as much as you could? Why do I care about merge vs. rebase? I pulled some bad code from a coworker that broke everything! How do I use reflog to time jump back to the good state I was in before? What&amp;rsquo;s an interactive rebase and how do I squash commits? I have legacy code in SVN/Mercurial, how can I get it into Git while preserving commit history?</description></item><item><title>Dependencies Demystified</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/dependencies-demystified-225072098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 13:40:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/dependencies-demystified-225072098/</guid><description>Dependency injection. Inversion of control. Containers. Let&amp;rsquo;s cut through the confusion and hyperbole and talk about what this really is. We&amp;rsquo;ll cover dependencies - why you should care, what they are, how you identify them, and when they provide value. We&amp;rsquo;ll also cover containers and how they can be used to effectively manage your dependencies.
Our speaker is Jason Bock. Jason is a Practice Lead for Magenic and a Microsoft MVP (C#).</description></item><item><title>Cozy Up To Your (Bash) Shell</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/cozy-up-to-your-bash-shell-223786319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 09:33:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/cozy-up-to-your-bash-shell-223786319/</guid><description>If you use OS X or ever interact with Linux or BSD, learning a few things about the shell (Terminal) can give you a big boost in productivity. Jackson Murtha will be giving a brief practical introduction to bash-like shells and basic unix command line paradigms like GNU utilities and piping. The talk will introduce basic tools, language features, and concepts which are common or have a high productivity return.</description></item><item><title>Git Workshop</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/git-workshop-223269129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 16:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/git-workshop-223269129/</guid><description>MWOP and I are putting together a patchwork inspired git workshop(bring your own device). Whether you&amp;rsquo;re new to git or quite experienced hopefully you can come learn something. The workshop centers around content produced by github is designed to be hands-on and self paced, but we&amp;rsquo;ll have more than a few mentors available for questions.
If you&amp;rsquo;re already using git (or another dvcs) and want to talk workflow, or related things like continuous integration/delivery feel free to come tell others what you&amp;rsquo;re doing or ask what they&amp;rsquo;re doing.</description></item><item><title>Taming Asynchronicity with Promises</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/taming-asynchronicity-with-promises-220614398/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 19:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/taming-asynchronicity-with-promises-220614398/</guid><description>Talk Repo
What are promises and how can they be managed? Bob Davidson from Blend Interactive will introduce this new fascination of the Javascript community. He&amp;rsquo;ll also discuss some functional programming techniques to help get you out of code &amp;ldquo;nesting hell&amp;rdquo;, and explain why the difference between asynchronous and multithreaded programming matters. The examples will be in Javascript, but apply to many other languages.
Note: Not at the Raven training building.</description></item><item><title>NodeJS Workshop - Streams (don't cross them. It would be bad)</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/nodejs-workshop-streams-don-t-cross-them-it-would-be-bad-219519249/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 13:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/nodejs-workshop-streams-don-t-cross-them-it-would-be-bad-219519249/</guid><description>Starting off the new year with another NodeSchool workshop. This one is all about working with streams. Streams are introduced in the initial Learn You Node and continued in considerably more depth here.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in a more advanced workshop or one of introductory ones there will be mentors available to help with any of them.
Have something you want to hear about, or something you want to speak about?</description></item><item><title>Middleware with MWOP</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/middleware-with-mwop-217647132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 15:26:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/middleware-with-mwop-217647132/</guid><description>Lots of web frameworks are being built around the idea of shared middleware these days(Rack, WSGI, OWIN, Connect, etc). Matthew Weier O&amp;rsquo;Phinney will be talking about the benefits of compose-able middleware in Connect. Seth Larson will have information about the similar approach being taken in ASP.Net vNext</description></item><item><title>Building SPAs with the MEAN Stack</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/building-spas-with-the-mean-stack-206649952/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 13:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/building-spas-with-the-mean-stack-206649952/</guid><description>From prototyping to production, having a light stack can simplify and speed up application development. MongoDB, ExpressJS, Angular and NodeJS team up and form one of web-dev’s latest stacks and in this session we will cover how to build single page applications using these four tools.</description></item><item><title>SICP Discussion</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhyslbzb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2014 15:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhyslbzb/</guid><description>For August 19th, we&amp;rsquo;ll be covering section 4.1.
A nice pdf of the book: https://github.com/sarabander/sicp-pdf/blob/master/sicp.pdf
Public Github Repo for exercises in Clojure: https://github.com/hipplej/sicp</description></item><item><title>NodeJS Workshop - Async</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/nodejs-workshop-async-184188452/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2014 15:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/nodejs-workshop-async-184188452/</guid><description>Nodeschool.io Async module, bring your own device.
http://nodeschool.io/#asyncyou</description></item><item><title>Serious Node with Bryan Burgers</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/serious-node-with-bryan-burgers-183035112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 08:57:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/serious-node-with-bryan-burgers-183035112/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve heard of Node.js. You&amp;rsquo;ve even played around with it. But is it a fad? Should you use it at work? Why Node is serious, what makes it a reasonable choice for a long term project, and how to introduce it into your business.</description></item><item><title>Hack night</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/hack-night-174535112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 14:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/hack-night-174535112/</guid><description>By demand, this is a night for members who are stuck or want feedback to bring in anything and talk to others input. Any kind of technical problem as long as it deals with creating or delivering applications is welcome.</description></item><item><title>You Don't Need jQuery</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/you-don-t-need-jquery-174469222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2014 09:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/you-don-t-need-jquery-174469222/</guid><description>As a developer, one of the first things you do when starting a new project is include jQuery and start writing code. That’s the way it’s always been, and works for you. Stop it. Devices are getting smaller, processors are getting slower, and web apps are more complicated. jQuery can cause some fairly serious performance issues. So let’s take a step back from jQuery and talk about ways VanillaJS is faster and simpler.</description></item><item><title>Reactive Extensions with Jason Bock</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/reactive-extensions-with-jason-bock-169154452/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 01:19:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/reactive-extensions-with-jason-bock-169154452/</guid><description>It’s typical in software development to pull data from different sources. However, in the modern world of asynchronicity, data is being retrieved in real-time streams, akin to how developers handle events. Reactive Extensions is a library that makes it easier to code in a reactive, asynchronous, composable style. In this session, you’ll get a gentle introduction into this library and how its API works.
About the speaker:
Jason Bock is a Practice Lead for Magenic (http://www.</description></item><item><title>NodeJS Workshop #1</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/nodejs-workshop-1-168186132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 09:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/nodejs-workshop-1-168186132/</guid><description>Every other month we&amp;rsquo;re doing workshops with various technologies starting with NodeJS. For March, we&amp;rsquo;ll be going through NodeSchool.IO&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Learn Node&amp;rdquo; module. This covers an introduction to nodejs from console.log through making asynchronous http requests.
Josh Broton, Seth Larson, and other members will be available to help people through any problems they run across. Attendees do have to supply their own computer(or pair with someone else who did).
If you attended our test run of this in January and completed Learn Node feel free to move on to Stream Adventure, Async, or one of the other modules.</description></item><item><title>SICP Discussion</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhysfbxb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhysfbxb/</guid><description>For March 18th, we&amp;rsquo;ll be covering the first two sections of Chapter 2.
A nice pdf of the book: https://github.com/sarabander/sicp-pdf/blob/master/sicp.pdf
Public Github Repo for exercises in Clojure: https://github.com/hipplej/sicp</description></item><item><title>SICP Discussion</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhysgbtb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhysgbtb/</guid><description>For April 15th, we&amp;rsquo;ll be covering sections 2.3 and 2.4.
A nice pdf of the book: https://github.com/sarabander/sicp-pdf/blob/master/sicp.pdf
Public Github Repo for exercises in Clojure: https://github.com/hipplej/sicp
Another public Github Repo for exercises in Racket and some in Lua:
https://github.com/Combatjuan/miscellus/tree/master/sicp</description></item><item><title>SICP Discussion</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhyshbbc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhyshbbc/</guid><description>For May 20th, we&amp;rsquo;ll be covering sections 2.5 and 3.1.
A nice pdf of the book: https://github.com/sarabander/sicp-pdf/blob/master/sicp.pdf
Public Github Repo for exercises in Clojure: https://github.com/hipplej/sicp
Public Github Repo for exercises in Racket:
https://github.com/Combatjuan/miscellus</description></item><item><title>SICP Discussion</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhysjbwb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 08:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-dgfnwhysjbwb/</guid><description>For June 17th, we&amp;rsquo;ll be covering 3.2 and 3.3
A nice pdf of the book: https://github.com/sarabander/sicp-pdf/blob/master/sicp.pdf
Public Github Repo for exercises in Clojure: https://github.com/hipplej/sicp</description></item><item><title>SICP Discussion, first meetup</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-first-meetup-165467072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 20:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/sicp-discussion-first-meetup-165467072/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll be covering the first chapter of SICP.
For more information on the Structure and Interpretation of Computer Programs, see (http://mitpress.mit.edu/sicp/ and http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Structure_and_Interpretation_of_Computer_Programs)</description></item><item><title>Apigility: Agile APIs w/ Matthew Weier O'Phinney</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/apigility-agile-apis-w-matthew-weier-o-phinney-162847112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2014 12:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/apigility-agile-apis-w-matthew-weier-o-phinney-162847112/</guid><description>You’re making the move to APIs – you have a mobile application, or you need to enable cross-organizational access to your data, or because you have an idea for a cool single page web application. Now you’re mired in learning everything you can about web services, and discovering that APIs pose a whole set of challenges discrete from your web applications: what response format should you use? how will you report errors?</description></item><item><title>NodeJS Workshop #0</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/nodejs-workshop-0-162311082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2014 09:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/nodejs-workshop-0-162311082/</guid><description>Getting back in the swing of things for 2014 we&amp;rsquo;re currently planning to do some NodeJS workshops on months we don&amp;rsquo;t have speakers. Starting off the year with Learn Node. Josh Broton, and Seth Larson(and likely other regular attendees) will be available to help people through any problems attendees run across. Bring your own computer.
This first meetup is trying out a new location, Raven Industries&amp;rsquo; Training Center. We&amp;rsquo;ll be trying to consistently schedule the last Tuesday of the month when hosting at Raven.</description></item><item><title>SD Code Camp</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/sd-code-camp-145882442/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 12:19:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/sd-code-camp-145882442/</guid><description>Sign up at: http://sdcodecamp.eventbrite.com</description></item><item><title>JavaScript and the New Virtual Machine: Scaling client and server</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/javascript-and-the-new-virtual-machine-scaling-client-and-server-139240462/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2013 10:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/javascript-and-the-new-virtual-machine-scaling-client-and-server-139240462/</guid><description>Scott Hanselman is in town to speak at Innovation Expo on tuesday and is awesome enough to talk with us on Monday. The time is a little earlier than usual, but we&amp;rsquo;ll have tacos so thats ok. We&amp;rsquo;re starting early so that those attending Inno Expo&amp;rsquo;s event tonight can make it to the latter part of that if they&amp;rsquo;d like.
Innovation Expo is a conference focusing on connecting entrepreneurs, innovators, angel investors, venture capitalists, and the many others who are involved in developing startup companies.</description></item><item><title>put the dev into ops (chef/vagrant)</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/put-the-dev-into-ops-chef-vagrant-125303982/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2013 17:34:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/put-the-dev-into-ops-chef-vagrant-125303982/</guid><description>An overview of the community edition of Chef by OpsCode and creating loval environments with it(15-45 minutes). Following discussion on how we(and you) go about making deploying updates an easy and seamless operation, at least as seamless as organization processes allow.
If anyone has used Puppet I&amp;rsquo;d love for input from them in how it compares/contrasts to Chef.
Any other deployment tools would also be open for discussion. Capistrano, Fabric, PSake are a few I&amp;rsquo;m familiar with that come to mind.</description></item><item><title>Responsive Web Design</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/responsive-web-design-120546172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2013 16:40:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/responsive-web-design-120546172/</guid><description>Josh Broton is going to lead a discussion on Responsive Web Design.</description></item><item><title>Compare and Contrast DVCS Tools (primarily git and mercurial)</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/compare-and-contrast-dvcs-tools-primarily-git-and-mercurial-118399832/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 13:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/compare-and-contrast-dvcs-tools-primarily-git-and-mercurial-118399832/</guid><description>Plan is to do a very short short (10 minutes?) centralized vs. distributed overview and then probably do an outline of some of the main different DVCS approaches. Then we&amp;rsquo;ll do a deep dive into the subtle differences between git &amp;amp; mercurial. (How branching is subtly different between the two, why reflog is amazing, how subrepos are handled differently, rebase vs. merge, etc.) I&amp;rsquo;m sure we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the different commandline and graphical user interface options for each as well at some point.</description></item><item><title>Open discussion on essential tools</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/open-discussion-on-essential-tools-111551542/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2013 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/open-discussion-on-essential-tools-111551542/</guid><description>Whatever you use for Development, Deployment, Testing, etc. Open discussion about problems you&amp;rsquo;ve ran into and how you and others have fixed or hacked around them.
People present will discuss (at a minimum) usage of: Git, Jenkins, Chef, homebrew, bash, powershell, sass and how they fit into your workflow.</description></item><item><title>ASP.Net Web API</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/asp-net-web-api-107094152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2013 12:53:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/asp-net-web-api-107094152/</guid><description>Joel Kauffman is covering anything or everything from consuming a Web API feed, to building your own. Including upcoming/new features like OData support and automatically generating help page documentation.
This session can also be caught the following saturday at Nebraska Code Camp: http://nebraskacodecamp.com/</description></item><item><title>Searching with Solr: An Introduction</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/searching-with-solr-an-introduction-92927012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2012 17:08:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/searching-with-solr-an-introduction-92927012/</guid><description>An introduction to using Apache Solr for implementing search.</description></item><item><title>Build Modern PHP Applications</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/build-modern-php-applications-90850022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 16:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/build-modern-php-applications-90850022/</guid><description>PHP has changed a lot in the last few releases. We&amp;rsquo;ll introduce some of the recent and upcoming changes, some of the new tools and frameworks they have enabled, and how you can utilize them to improve your PHP projects. As an example, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through development using the Symfony2 framework.</description></item><item><title>Discuss JavaScript Patterns</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/discuss-javascript-patterns-90849862/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2012 16:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/discuss-javascript-patterns-90849862/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ll talk about making javascript behave similar to other language people are more used to using. How to create constructors, inheritance, namespaces, modules, private/public properties, callbacks, etc. A primer for the introduction to nodejs I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to give in February which requires understanding of these patterns.
I&amp;rsquo;ll have some examples/notes but with how many people signed up to attend I know to have significant JS experience it would be foolish not to have this more discussion based.</description></item><item><title>Mike Benkovich presenting: Cross-Platform, Cross-Device, Connected-Apps Oh My!</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/mike-benkovich-presenting-cross-platform-cross-device-connected-apps-oh-my-86032232/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 10:08:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/mike-benkovich-presenting-cross-platform-cross-device-connected-apps-oh-my-86032232/</guid><description>Mike Benkovich is a Developer Evangelist at Microsoft and will be in town to talk about cross platform cross device connectivity in applications.
Today&amp;rsquo;s users don&amp;rsquo;t live on just a workstation or a laptop. With the proliferation of laptops, smart phones, and tablets people work from a variety of forms and clients. Building applications that can leverage a consistent view of identity, data and services will enable the workforce to be productive wherever they are.</description></item><item><title>OWASP SD Chapter Meeting</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/owasp-sd-chapter-meeting-83066032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2012 22:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/owasp-sd-chapter-meeting-83066032/</guid><description>WHERE University Center North (4801 N. Career Avenue - the building on the northwest corner of campus) - Room 149
AGENDA Refreshments will be provided by SDN Communications.
The October 2012 itinerary will be as follows:
Networking/Introductions
Chapter Business
Josh Stroschein will be presenting on hacking .NET applications (or disassembling .NET clients). This presentation will look at decompiling .NET applications for purposes such as security audits and spy/ad-ware analysis. The goal will be to decompile, alter and optionally recompile .</description></item><item><title>South Dakota Code Camp Q&amp;A</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/south-dakota-code-camp-q-a-82106892/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 16:13:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/south-dakota-code-camp-q-a-82106892/</guid><description>Anyone interested in speaking, attending, or sponsoring is welcome to come and ask questions.
People interested in or already committed to speaking can get together and hone what exactly they&amp;rsquo;d like to cover on their topics, or help someone come up with a good topic.
South Dakota Code Camp is November 10th. More information is available at - http://southdakotacodecamp.net</description></item><item><title>XNA and random followup discussion</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/xna-and-random-followup-discussion-68866082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 13:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/xna-and-random-followup-discussion-68866082/</guid><description>Alex Stommes from CHR will be talking about some various things he&amp;rsquo;s done with XNA development. The usual talk about how spaces are better than tabs will follow(or whatever people are interested in bringing up or asking about).</description></item><item><title>SD OWASP (RM 149)</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/sd-owasp-rm-149-61750302/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 09:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/sd-owasp-rm-149-61750302/</guid><description>Just incase anyone is interested, we have quarterly meetings at the University Center discussing web security and vulnerability exploitation.
https://www.owasp.org/index.php/South_Dakota</description></item><item><title>VS 2012, Web API, and jQuery</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/vs-2012-web-api-and-jquery-60842802/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 16:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/vs-2012-web-api-and-jquery-60842802/</guid><description>John Petersen is in town. He&amp;rsquo;ll be talking about Visual Studio 2012, Web API (the largest addition to asp.net mvc in v4).
John is an MVP, writes for CODE Magazine and CodeBetter, and has spoken at many other events. It&amp;rsquo;ll be awesome to him in town.
The jQuery portion of this is being rescheduled, but Q&amp;amp;A related to jQuery is still an open topic for questions after the presentation.
Blend Interactive is on the second floor above Child&amp;rsquo;s Play toys.</description></item><item><title>Knockout JS</title><link>https://sfdevs.com/events/knockout-js-58108212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2012 15:55:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfdevs.com/events/knockout-js-58108212/</guid><description>Kwen Peterson will be presenting some JavaScript goodness, starting with KnockoutJS, maybe more.
Some sort of food should be provided, open conversation about who is doing with with JS or other tools/processes/topics people would like to talk about to follow.</description></item></channel></rss>